队员席
欢迎关注微博@UUU字幕组，获取最新熟肉信息！
出品
UUU字幕组
翻译
草
校对
Husky
特效
presisco
压制
SG
谢谢你的薯渣, 皮弟!
Thanks for the bits, Peedee.
对, 还有 告诉罗纳多
Oh, and tell Ronaldo
我希望他脸上的红疹能赶快好起来
I hope his weird rash clears up soon.
生活真是艰难啊, 对不?
Life can get really intense, huh?
是啊, 尤其是你的人生
Yeah, especially your life.
来瞧瞧 -- 外星人绑架事件
Let's see -- alien abduction.
外太空人类动物园一日游
Going to a weird zoo for humans in space.
还有从两个
And sneaking out
星际暴君眼皮底下溜走!
right past a pair of intergalactic tyrants!
不过, 最后总能会安全回到
Well, it's nice to know
像今天这样和平的日子中
we can still have peaceful days like this
这是最好的
without any trouble.
唔, 呃
Mm. Oof.
差一点点
Almost.
嘿, 小朋友们!
Hey, kids!
放下手中的薯渣, 放下它们!
Drop those fry bits. Drop 'em!
哦不, 是警察!
Oh, no, it's the cops!
常年购买地下菜单
All the years of ordering off menu
它的报应总算是来嘲讽我了!
have finally come back to taunt me!
你是想说它们开始缠扰你吗?
You mean haunt you?
史蒂文, 那辆车根本不是警车
Steven, that's not even a police car.
-那只是个... -我投降!
-It's just... -I surrender!
我知道我这么做是犯法的
I knew I was breaking the rules,
但…我却没有停下!
but... I did it anyway!
我已经嗑薯渣嗑到精神失常了!
The bits had their hooks in me!
爸爸, 别再逗他了
Dad, quit joking around.
真是的, 康妮!
Come on, Connie!
我差点就骗过他了
I almost had him.
莫雪伦先生?
Mr. Maheswaran?
哇哦, 我可没想到他会当真啊
Wow, I didn't think he'd take it that seriously.
你还好吗, 史蒂文?
You okay there, Steven?
哦没问题, 地上还挺舒服的
Oh, yeah. I love it down here.
我勇敢的小剑士怎么样啊?
And how's my swashbuckling swashbuckler doing?
我很好
I'm good.
你知道吗史蒂文, 你估计是有点脱水
You know, Steven, maybe you're dehydrated.
都是因为晚饭前吃那么多垃圾食品
Probably from eating that garbage before dinner.
充满敬意地告诉您, 薯渣可不是垃圾食品
Respectfully, fry bits are not garbage.
别担心史蒂文, 他只是在逗你玩
Don't worry, Steven. He's just messing with you.
抱歉啦史蒂文, 快起来吧
Sorry, Steven. Let's get you up.
你在海滩市干嘛呢爸爸?
What are you even doing in Beach City, Dad?
实际上我来这里有工作要做
I'm out here on a job, actually.
我工作的那个私人安保公司
The private security company I work for
收到了一位名叫哈罗德.微笑先生的来电
got a call from a Mr. Harold Smiley
说有人潜伏在游乐园附近
stating that someone's been lurking around Funland
在乐园打烊之后
after hours.
所以我今晚一整晚都要呆在这里
So, I'll be here all night...
在附近盯梢
on a stakeout.
哇啊, 盯梢!
Whoa, a stakeout!
爸爸, 这太酷了!
Dad, that's so cool!
对吧, 挺酷的不是吗?
Yeah, itispretty cool, huh?
保护海滩市的居民
Protecting the citizens of Beach City.
就像你们一样!
Just like you guys!
这不是很有趣吗, 史蒂文?
Wouldn't that be fun, Steven?
我有机会也想在哪里盯梢
I'd love to go on a stakeout sometime.
或许你们几个今晚能帮上忙
Maybe you guys could help out tonight.
-什么?! -什么?!
-What?! -What?!
我们不算正规的安保人员也可以吗?
Even though we're not officially sanctioned security personnel?
嘿, 没什么大不了的
Hey, why not?
估计就是附近哪个小伙子在游荡
It's probably just some kid loitering.
嘿, 小朋友!
Hey, kid!
对, 就是你!
Yes, hello?
你头上的警示牌写着禁止游荡
The sign above you says no loitering.
这群人真是一代比一代年轻
They get younger every year.
所以, 你们准备好了嘛?
So, y'all ready for this?
有些年轻人可是会说脏话的哦
Some of these teens can use some pretty strong language.
嘿, 史蒂文, 你想来一起帮忙毁掉某个小年轻的夜晚吗?
Hey, Steven, you want to help ruin some teen's night?
随时愿意
Always.
海滩边没什么异常
Coast is all clear behind us.
一切看上去都挺安静的
Things seem pretty quiet so far.
哈, 当然啦
Well, yeah.
有咱们在这里守着, 没人会想越过栅栏的
Nobody's even gonna try hopping the fence with us here.
但没人知道会发生什么
But you never know.
有时候, 我甚至会从车内走出去
Sometimes, I actually leave the car.
-哇哦 -哇哦
-Wow. -Wow.
估计你们在拯救世界的时候
I'm sure you guys do lots of waiting
也常需要长时间潜伏
when you're saving the world.
你们也总不会一直干仗
It can't be all bam, pow action all the time.
啊, 我倒希望那样
Aw, I wish.
我们的确老是在干仗
There's a lot of fighting.
我是指, 某种意义上 我继承了一场星际战争
I mean, I kind of inherited an intergalactic war.
嘿, 爸爸, 这个纸箱子是干嘛的
Hey, Dad, what's this box?
哦, 这是我刚刚没收了的东西
Oh, I just confiscated that
是一个小伙计在服装店偷的
from a kid who was shoplifting in a costume shop.
喔啊
Whoa!
你完全可以用它们做伪装啊!
You could totally use these for disguises.
你有没有想过…变个装?
Don't you ever need to go...undercover?
你怎么知道我现在没有变装呢?
How do you know I'm not undercover right now?
开玩笑的
Just kidding.
我戴眼镜因为我近视
I need these to see.
但如果你们想玩玩那些东西
But if you guys want to play with that stuff,
随便玩
go ahead.
好的
Okay.
嗯, 我想玩玩变装
Well, I want to be undercover.
变装成…
I'll be...
维罗尼卡 库卡曼卡
Veronica Cucamonga.
而我是, 意大利的彼得 比萨波波里斯
It's a-me, Peter Pizzapoppolis from Italia!
比萨波波利斯? 听上去像个希腊名
Pizzapoppolis? That sounds Greek.
你确定你不想变装吗, 爸爸?
You sure you don't want anything, Dad?
这里还有个小丑鼻子
There's a clown nose back here.
不谢了
No, thanks.
保安可不是什么玩笑
Being a security guard is no joke,
所以他们给每个保安都装备了这个宝贝
which is why they equip us with these.
哇哦! 手电筒!
Wow! A flashlight!
没错
Yeah.
有时 世界会非常黑暗的
It gets pretty dark out there.
那是什么?
What was that?
妈妈咪呀, 我的栅栏呀!
Mama mia! The fence-a!
这是怎么做到的?
How on earth did this happen?
如果这是某个混球用钳子剪的
If this were some punk with a pair of bolt cutters,
那也会是个整齐的切口
this would be a clean cut.
但这根铁链看上去像是被直接撕断的
But this chain looks like it was torn apart.
这可不是哪个小鬼做的
This was no kid.
好吧, 如果不是哪个误入歧途的年轻人
Well, if it wasn't a misguided teen,
又会是谁干的呢?
what could it be?
这就是我们的任务了
It's up to us to find out.
听上去是调查时间了
Sounds like we better investigate.
库卡曼卡, 比萨波波利斯
Cucamonga, Pizzapoppolis.
-在! -在!
-Right! -Right!
嗯?
Huh?
有人吗? 保安巡逻!
Hello? This is security!
你现在在闯入了私人领地
You are trespassing on private property.
不要试图给自己做炸热狗吃
Do not attempt to make yourself a corn dog.
欢乐园公司法人没有义务对
Funland Incorporated is not liable
无执照的油炸锅使用者
for the harm you may incur while trying to operate
可能发生的事故负责
a deep fryer without a license.
你需要执照才能用炸锅?
You need a license to operate a deep fryer?
喔啊
Whoa.
嘿, 请止步!
Hey, stop right there!
跟上我
Follow my lead.
不许动!
Don't move!
我们跟丢了?
Did we lose them?
他们咋溜那么快哒?
Which a-way did they go so fast-a?
闭上嘴巴, 打开你的眼睛跟耳朵
Mouths closed, eyes and ears open.
嗯嗯
Hmm. Hmm.
糟糕的举动, 蠢货
Bad move, chump.
这艘飞船离不开地球咯
That space ship's permanently earthbound.
抓住你啦! 我是说 不许动!
Gotcha! I mean freeze!
哦天啊
Oh, man.
我们这是摊上了哪个逃脱艺术家了吗?
Are we dealing with some sort of escape artist?
嘿, 史蒂文, 或许我们应该把武器拿出来
Hey, Steven, maybe we should get our weapons.
这不必要的
That won't be necessary.
我们不需要恶化现在的状况
We're not here to escalate the situation.
再说, 一个好的保安
Besides, a good security guard
只需要一个可靠的手电
only needs their trusty flashlight.
嘿! 快开门!
Hey! Open up this instant!
对, 放我们出去!
Yeah, let us out!
-这个设施启动了! -它启动了!
-The ride's moving! -The ride's moving!
-我们得赶快关上它!  -别担心
-We got to shut it off!  -Don't worry.
吃我一手电
I'll just use my trusty flashlight.
哦不!
Oh, no!
牛顿的力量!
The laws of physics!
嗷!
Ow!
你还好吗爸爸? 没问题
You okay, Dad? Yeah.
而且我想到了个新点子
I've got a new idea, though.
这回, 我要换个角度扔它
This time, I'll throw it at an angle.
爸, 我不觉得这有用! 走你!
Dad, I don't think that'll work. Go!
啊! !
Aah!
我们得从这个辣肉丸子里逃出去!!
We got to get out of this spicy meatball!
嘿 这块地方没在转
Hey, this part isn't moving at all.
史蒂文!
Steven!
对不起!
Sorry!
听着, 你这个健美狂魔逃脱艺术家罪犯
Listen, you bodybuilding escape artist criminal,
这可不是什么游戏
this isn't a game.
你可是威胁到了一个在岗执法人员和俩未成年人的生命安全
You've endangered an officer of the law and two small children.
快快束手就擒 否则后果严重!
Show yourself before you get into serious trouble!
史蒂文, 你觉不觉得
Steven, do you think
这有可能是某个宝石怪物或者变异体干的?
maybe it's some kind of Gem mutant or monster?
有可能, 但它试图困住咱们
It could be, but it trapped us.
宝石怪物和变异体没有这么聪明
The monsters and mutants aren't that smart.
那我们有可能在对付一个母星宝石人吗?
Could we be dealing with a Homeworld Gem?
母星? 宝石怪? 变异体?
Homeworld? Gem? Mutant?
呃, 不管这是什么东西
I, uh -- well, whatever it is,
如果有人闯入这里, 他们要先过我这一关
if someone's trespassing, they'll have to answer to me.
好安静
It's so quiet.
我简直不敢相信
I can't believe this.
他们在嘲讽我们
They're mocking us.
快现身吧!
Show yourself!
你到底想要什么?
What is it that you want here?
奖品? 欢乐?
Prizes? Fun?
你觉得这是你找乐子的地方?
You think this is the place to get your kicks?
你这个变态怪物
You sick monster.
摧毁了这个欢乐之园的圣洁!
Destroying the sanctity of this land of fun!
你身后!
Behind you!
爸爸!
Dad!
莫雪伦先生!
Mr. Maheswaran!
呃, 不要担心, 我没事的
Uh, don't worry. I'm fine.
只是 -- 他们在那里!
Just -- there they are!
快来, 史蒂文!
Come on, Steven!
你们先走我殿后!
I'm right behind you!
你这回可逃不掉了!
You're not getting away this time!
卧靠这么多口香糖!
That's a lot of gumballs!
快跳!
Jump!
啊啊啊啊!
Aah!
此路不通
放弃吧!
It's time to give up!
你已经无路可逃了!
There's no way out!
口香糖?
Gumballs?
啊啊啊啊啊!
Aaaaah!
嘿, 孩子们
Hey, kids.
罪魁祸首就在这角落里, 爹地
The culprit's at the end of this corner, Dad.
干得漂亮, 你们俩
Good work, you two.
现在, 来瞧瞧这家伙的真面目吧
Now, let's shed some light on this subject.
等等
Wait.
洋葱!
Onion!
是你?
You?
你在这儿干嘛呢?
What are you doing here?
我们正在进行一场严肃的调查
We're in the middle of a very important investigation.
爸爸, 我觉得他就是我们要找的人
Dad, I think this is who's been causing all this trouble.
洋葱, 是我, 史蒂文
Onion, it's me, Steven.
史蒂文宇宙
Steven Universe.
这是莫雪伦先生
That's just Mr. Maheswaran.
哦, 我的天啊
Oh, my gosh,
你以为追你的是一群陌生人?
did you think a bunch of strangers were chasing you?
怪不得跑得比兔子还快
No wonder you were trying to throw us off your trail.
洋葱, 没事
Onion, everything's okay.
这不可能是一个孩子干的
It can't just be a kid.
这不合理!
It doesn't make any sense!
那个巨大的影子呢?
What about that huge shadow?
我觉得那是因为他在手电下显得高大
I think the flashlight just made him look big.
但那个栅栏是被硬扯开的
But the fence was ripped apart!
他有用过喷灯的前科
I have seen him use a blowtorch before.
我还找到了这块卡在栅栏里的布料
I also found this piece of fabric stuck in the fence.
当然了
Of course.
从来不会有什么大事发生
It's never actually something.
怎么了?
What's wrong?
没什么
Nothing's wrong.
只是我的工作不像
It's just my job isn't like
你和史蒂文的那些刺激的冒险
the exhilerating adventures you've been having with Steven
或你妈妈在医院的那些
or the life-threatening emergencies
生死攸关的情况
your mom deals with at the hospital.
我的工作的高潮也就是叫小鬼们不要到处闲逛
The most action I see is telling kids to quit loitering around.
我就是希望
I was hoping
你们能看到我认真工作
maybe you'd get to see me take on a serious job,
但我想我最擅长的还是
but I guess all I'm good at
继续当你蠢蠢的老爹
is being your silly, old dad.
你说的对
You're right.
你是挺蠢的
You are silly,
但这就是为什么我们愿意跟你在一起
but that's why I like hanging out with you.
我的生活中太多沉重的负担
I've got enough serious things going on in my life.
有时候我只希望能多花些时间跟我的父亲在一起
Sometimes I just want to spend time with my dad.
谢谢你
Thanks.
你是我的财富呢, 弗罗妮卡 库卡曼卡
You're a keeper, Veronica Cucamonga.
好吧, 孩子们, 看来这都是一场误解
Well, kid, this may have been a big misunderstanding,
但你还是要为这个栅栏负责
but you're still in trouble for this fence.
哦, 当然你要
Oh, yes, you are.
这次就饶了他吧
Just let him off the hook on this one.
我们已经快把他吓死了
We already scared him straight.
他这个年纪法律也会饶了他吧
The law must be different for someone his age.
你知错了吗?
You learned your lesson?
那就可以走了
Then you're free to go.
还有记住, 小伙子, 别没事瞎逛了
And remember, kid, no loitering.
我都不知道我该怎么跟上面汇报了
I don't know how I'm gonna explain this back at the office.